

Abdullatif Jarkas

O Home: Banias, Tartus, Syria

Email: abdullatif.jarkas1@gmail.com

Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/abdullatif.jarkas.1

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/abdullatif-jarkas/

Gender: Male **Date of birth:** 01/01/2003 **Nationality:** Syrian

ABOUT ME

A highly motivated Informatics Engineering student at Tishreen University, specializing in front-end development. With a strong background in leading frontend teams and a passion for creating visually appealing and user-friendly interfaces, I am dedicated to advancing my skills and knowledge in the tech industry. Currently based in Baniyas, Tartus, Syria, I bring a unique blend of academic excellence and hands-on experience that sets me apart as a valuable asset in any development team.

EDUCATION AND TRAIN-ING

[22/10/2020 – Current] Informatics Engineering

Tishreen University https://www.tishreen.edu.sy/

City: Lattakia | **Country:** Syria |

[01/07/2023 - 01/12/2023] Front-End Development Internship

Focal X Agency www.focal-x.com

City: Lattakia | Country: Syria |

[01/02/2024 - Current] Full-Stack Deploma Internship

Focal X Agency www.focal-x.com

City: Lattakia | Country: Syria |

WORK EXPERIENCE

[01/11/2023 - 01/01/2024] **Front End Developer**

Focal X Agency

City: Lattakia | Country: Syria

- I worked in a team on a project called AI website, and i implemented the website design as a front end developer using React is

[01/12/2023 - 01/02/2024]

Front End Developer

Focal X Agency

City: Lattakia | Country: Syria

- I worked in a team on a website, and i implemented the website design as a front end developer using React js , react-slick and React-Bootstrap

[01/02/2024 - Current] Front End Supervisor

Focal X Agency

City: Lattakia | Country: Syria

- I help Front End Interns improve thier skills in Front End development
- I correct their tasks.

DIGITAL SKILLS

My Digital Skills

React Frame Work | HTML | CSS | JavaScript | TypeScript | Version Control System (Git) | Github | Bootstrap

PROJECTS

[02/03/2024 - 17/03/2024] **VILLA**

VILLA is a website where you can Schedule a visit to a wide collection of Luxury villas, penthounses, Modern Condos and Appartments, so you can choose your dream property

Links: https://abdullatif-jarkas.github.io/task1 front fullstack/ https:// github.com/abdullatif-jarkas/task1 front fullstack

[01/08/2023 - 10/08/2023] **Learner**

Learner is a website where you can explore courses and become an instructor.

Links: https://abdullatif-jarkas.github.io/Task4_2/ https://github.com/abdullatifjarkas/Task4 2

[22/09/2023 - 06/10/2023] **PHONO**

Phono is a website where you can explore the world of tech, see the latest mobile phones and the latest news in the field of technology

Links: https://abdullatif-jarkas.github.io/Task5_2/ https://github.com/abdullatif-jarkas.github.io/Task5_2/ jarkas/Task5_2.git

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): Arabic

Other language(s):

English

LISTENING A2 READING A2 WRITING B1

SPOKEN PRODUCTION B2 SPOKEN INTERACTION B1

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user